Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Faculty files, 1946 -- 2018; UA252.005; 18 Linear Feet
  - Levin, Dr. James (Vet. School), 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.025.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Levine, Charna (Child Development), 1997-08-08 -- 1997-08-08; UA252.005.025.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Levine, Herbert (Medical), 1999 -- 2006; UA252.005.026.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Levine, Philip (Liberal Arts/Poetry), 1980-02-20 -- 1987-09-19; UA252.005.026.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Levine, Stephen H. (Liberal Arts/Engineering), 1980 -- 1988-04; UA252.005.026.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Levinson, Jim (Nutrition), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.026.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Levy, Barry (Medical School), 1993 -- 1994-02-14; UA252.005.026.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Levi, Robert I. M.D. (Medical School), 1981-02-12 -- 1983-06-10; UA252.005.026.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Levy, Stuart (Medical School), 1980-11 -- 1998-08-07; UA252.005.026.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Kim (chemical Engineering), 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.026.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Sara (Biology), 1991-12 -- 1992-01; UA252.005.026.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Li, Jinyu (Asian Languages), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.026.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Lichtenstein, Alice (Nutrition), 1993 -- 1999-10; UA252.005.026.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lieberman, Dr. Judy, 1992 -- 1993; UA252.005.026.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Linsenmayer, Dr. Thomas (Medical School), 1985-10-19 -- 1991-09; UA252.005.026.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Liscum, Laura (Medical School), 1986-08-27 -- 1986-09-10; UA252.005.026.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Locke, David (Liberal Arts/Music), 1981-09-22 -- 1998; UA252.005.026.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Lockeretz, William (School of Nutrition), 1981-08-14 -- 2000; UA252.005.026.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Loew, Dean Franklin (Veterinary School), 1986-08-27 -- 2003-05-14; UA252.005.026.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Lonero, Charles (Campus Police), 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.026.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Looby, Dr. George (Veterinary School), 1984-08-09 -- 1985-03-14; UA252.005.026.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Lopes, Paul (Sociology & Anthro), 1994-11-14 -- 1996-09-23; UA252.005.026.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Datcher-Loury, Linda (Economics), 1990-09 -- 1990-09; UA252.005.026.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Ludden, John (Medical), 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.026.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lundy, Lawrence (Medical School), 1990 -- 1994; UA252.005.026.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Luria, Zella (Liberal Arts/Psychology), 1964-09-20 -- 2018-06-17; UA252.005.026.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Lynch, Margaret (Biology), 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.026.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Macdonnell, Dr. Kenneth (Medical School), 1987-02-26 -- 1987-02-26; UA252.005.026.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Machata, Dr. John (Medical School), 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.026.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Maddox, Keith (Psychology), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.026.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Madias, Nicolaos E. M.D. (Medical School), 1982-12 -- 2000; UA252.005.026.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Madoc-Jones, Dr. Hywel (Medical School), 1987-11-05 -- 1987-11-05; UA252.005.026.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Madoff, Dr. Morton A. (Medical School), 1981-12-02 -- 1998-01-09; UA252.005.026.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Magness, Jodi (Classics), 1994-11-14 -- 1994-11-14; UA252.005.026.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Maguire, Kerry (Dental), 1999 -- 2000; UA252.005.026.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - McLellan, Andrew (Art History), 1993-08 -- 2012-01-20; UA252.005.026.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - McCreary, Carolyn (Engineering), 1998 -- 1999-03; UA252.005.026.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - McDonald, David R., 1990-03-06 -- 1996; UA252.005.026.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - McDonald, John (Music), 1993-09 -- 2003; UA252.005.026.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - McGuill, Michael (Veterinary School), 1994 -- 1997; UA252.005.026.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - McGurty, Tom (Administration), 1998-03-26 -- 1998-03-26; UA252.005.026.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - McIntosh, Leah (A&S), 2006 -- 2013; UA252.005.026.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - McKinnon, David (Mathematics), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.026.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - McKnight, Lee (Fletcher), 1974 -- 1978; UA252.005.026.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - McLennan, William (Chaplain), 1985-03-26 -- 1999-11-09; UA252.005.026.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - McMillan, Margaret (Economics), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.026.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Meagher, Robert (Fletcher School), 1966-10-27 -- 1987-04-09; UA252.005.026.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Meakin, John (Mech. Engineering), 1991-04 -- 1991-04; UA252.005.026.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Megerle, Don (Athletics/Swimming), 1972-01-07 -- 1996; UA252.005.026.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Mehta, Noshir (Dental), 1986-11-18 -- 2004; UA252.005.026.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Mejias, Dr. Judith E. (Faculty and Staff), 1981-12-07 -- 1983-02-23; UA252.005.026.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Meldon, Jerry [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1980-09-12 -- 1986-05-15; UA252.005.026.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Munro, Hamish (Director of Nutrition Research Center), 1981-05-17 -- 1988-09; UA252.005.026.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Munsat, Theodore (Medical School), 1981-05-12 -- 1990-05; UA252.005.026.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Miczek, Klaus, 1978 -- 1998; UA252.005.026.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 53)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press releases/faculty profile/magazine article/academic papers/curriculum vitae/biographic data sheet
  - Milburn, Nancy, 1964 -- 1985; UA252.005.026.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 54)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/letters/event program/faculty news
  - Milburn, Richard H., 1964 -- 1985; UA252.005.026.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 55)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/letters/faculty news/press releases
  - Miller, Laurie, 1996 -- 2002; UA252.005.026.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Miller, Lawrence, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.026.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Miller, Lloyd, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.026.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Miler, Robert L'Hommedieu, 1983 -- 1985; UA252.005.026.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 59)
    newspaper clipping/press release/resume
  - Miller, Russell, 1964 -- 1987; UA252.005.026.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 60)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/press releases/sketch/personnel record/faculty news/biography/academic paper/retirement resolution
  - Milner, Lockie, 1999 -- 2000; UA252.005.026.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Milyo, Jeffrey, 1994 -- 2000; UA252.005.026.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Minear, Larry, 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.026.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Miraglia, Vincent, 1984 -- 1991; UA252.005.026.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Mirowski, Philip, 1982 -- 1989; UA252.005.026.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Mitchell, George, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.026.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Moomaw, William, 1988 -- 2003; UA252.005.026.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 67)
    photos/newspaper clippings/pamphlet/press releases
  - Moore, Antony, 1995 -- 1998; UA252.005.026.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Moore, Claire L., 1987 -- 1998; UA252.005.026.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Moorehead, James, 1990 -- 1993; UA252.005.026.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Morgan, John, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.026.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Morita, Kiyoko, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.026.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Morris, Elisabeth, 1990 -- 1991; UA252.005.026.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Morse, Chirstopher, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.026.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Morsy, Soheir, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.026.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Moss, Larry Gene, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.026.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Mufti, Malik, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.026.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Mukand, Sharun, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.026.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Mulholland, Daniel, 1960 -- 1980; UA252.005.026.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Mumford, George S., 1957 -- 1989; UA252.005.026.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 26, Folder 80)
    photos/newspaper clippings/public information fact sheet/press releases/magazine/magazine article/personnel record/academic papers
  - Mumme, Donna L., 1999 -- 2003; UA252.005.027.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Paradis, M. R., 1983 -- 1998; UA252.005.027.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Park, Heh-Rahn, 1995; UA252.005.027.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Park, Ted, 1997; UA252.005.027.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Passamonti, Gino, 1980; UA252.005.027.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Pastore, John O., 1982 -- 1988; UA252.005.027.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Patronek, Gary, 1998 -- 2000; UA252.005.027.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Patterson, Sarah, 1980 -- 1989; UA252.005.027.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Patzak, Thomas, 2000; UA252.005.027.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Pauker, tephen G., 1979 -- 1991; UA252.005.027.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 10)
    photos/newspaper clippings/academic article
  - Pavletic, Michael M., 1983 -- 1996; UA252.005.027.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 11)
    photos/newspaper clippings/magazine clipping/news clip data sheet/press releases
  - Paydarfar, David, 1992; UA252.005.027.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Peecher, Susan, 2005; UA252.005.027.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Pechenik, Jan A., 1981 -- 1999; UA252.005.027.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 14)
    photos/newspaper clippings/faculty notes
  - Penvenne, Jeanne, 1990 -- 2001; UA252.005.027.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Pepall, Lynne, 1992 -- 1997; UA252.005.027.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Perry, John Curtis, 1981 -- 1997; UA252.005.027.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    photos/newspaper clippings/resume/pamphlet/event program/academic article/notes
  - Perry, John O., 1964 -- 1989; UA252.005.027.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    photos/newspaper clippings/retirement resolution/faculty news/letters/personnel record
  - Persaud, Ingrid, 1996 -- 1997; UA252.005.027.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Peterson, Eva, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.027.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Pfatzgraff, Robert L., 1980 -- 1997; UA252.005.027.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 21)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biographical blurb/curriculum vitae/college bulletin/magazine articles
  - Phillips, Joanne, 1981 -- 1995; UA252.005.027.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Pies, Ronald, 1985 -- 1992; UA252.005.027.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Piggford, George, 1997; UA252.005.027.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Pike,Arthur L., 1964 -- 1988; UA252.005.027.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Pinderhughes, Ellen, 2004; UA252.005.027.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Pitcher, Evelyn, 1959 -- 1986; UA252.005.027.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 27)
    photos/newspaper clippings/academic papers/retirement resolution/letters/faculty news/press releases/school bulletin/resume/personnel record/biographical data sheet
  - Pitkin, Mark R., 1995 -- 1998; UA252.005.027.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 28)
    photos/magazine clippings/press releases
  - Piwnica-Worms, Helen, 1992; UA252.005.027.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Plaut, Dr. Andrew, 1994 -- 1998; UA252.005.027.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Ramphele, Mamphele, 1980 -- 1989; UA252.005.027.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Rand, William M., 1989; UA252.005.027.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Rappaport, Ann, 1997; UA252.005.027.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Ramsmussen, Helen, 1984; UA252.005.027.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Ray, Sharon, 2003; UA252.005.027.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Reece, Robert M., 1998; UA252.005.027.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 36)
    photo/magazine clipping
  - Reed, Michael, 1996; UA252.005.027.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 37)
    photo/biographical blurb
  - Reichel, William, 1990 -- 1999; UA252.005.027.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Reichlin, Seymour, 1980 -- 1987; UA252.005.027.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Reid, Peter, 1984 -- 1985; UA252.005.027.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 40)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book introduction
  - Reindollar, Richard, 1990 -- 1999; UA252.005.027.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Reinisch, Carol, 1983 -- 1997; UA252.005.027.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Reitman, Bruce, 1976 -- 1993; UA252.005.027.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 43)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letters
  - Remick, Elizabeth J., 1997; UA252.005.027.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Reschovsky, Andrew, 1980 -- 1989; UA252.005.027.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 45)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/academic papers/magazine article
  - Reschovsky, Andrew, 1986; UA252.005.027.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 46)
    photos/academic reports/newspaper clipping
  - Reuss, Robert L., 1980 -- 1987; UA252.005.027.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 47)
    newspaper clippings/biographical data sheet/curriculum vitae
  - Reynolds, Marion, 1997; UA252.005.027.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Phillips, Joanne, 1984 -- 1990; UA252.005.027.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Richert, Clemens, 1995; UA252.005.027.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Richmond, John, 1986 -- 1987; UA252.005.027.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 51)
    photo/newspaper clippings/press release
  - Rider, Virginia, 1988 -- 1990; UA252.005.027.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Ridge, John, 1998; UA252.005.027.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Rinke, Stefan, 1999; UA252.005.027.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Rissin, Louis, 1997; UA252.005.027.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Rivard, David, 1988 -- 1991; UA252.005.027.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 56)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book review/fellowship announcement /resume
  - Rizzone, George P., 1979 -- 1981; UA252.005.027.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 57)
    newspaper clipping/letter/curriculum vitae
  - Robbat, Albert, 1986 -- 1992; UA252.005.027.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Robbins, Allison, 1997; UA252.005.027.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Ross, Linda Ann, 1985 -- 1998; UA252.005.027.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 60)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biographical data sheet/Curriculum Vitae/press release
  - Rothbaum, Fred, 1982 -- 1993; UA252.005.027.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Rothfeld, Glen, 1992; UA252.005.027.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Roubenoff, Ronenn, 1990 -- 1997; UA252.005.027.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 63)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press releases/academic papers
  - Rounds, Rebecca, 1997; UA252.005.027.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Murnane, Dr. Thomas, 1971-07-13 -- 2002; UA252.005.027.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Murtaugh, Dr. Robert (Faculty & Staff), 1987-01-29 -- 1998-07-09; UA252.005.027.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Must, Dr. Aviva (Nutrition), 1999 -- 2004; UA252.005.027.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Naginiski, Isabelle H. (Faculty & Staff), 1987-01-15 -- 2002; UA252.005.027.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Dr. Najjar, 1972-12-14 -- 1988-09; UA252.005.027.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Narnine, Edmund (Medical School), 1994; UA252.005.027.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Navia, Brad (Medical), 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.027.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Nelson, Charles Gerald (Instructor German), 1966-09-17 -- 1999; UA252.005.027.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Nelson, Frederick (Mech. Eng.), 1964-05-15 -- 1990-01-08; UA252.005.027.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Nelson, Miriam (Faculy & Staff), 1986-08-06 -- 1998-04-06; UA252.005.027.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - Nettelton, Joyce (Faculty), 1984 -- 1987-07-22; UA252.005.027.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 75)
  - Newell, Peggy (Administration), 1996 -- 1998; UA252.005.027.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 76)
  - Nitecki, Zbigniew, 1981-09-11 -- 1985-10; UA252.005.027.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 77)
  - Nitsche, Monika (mathematics), 1997-09-19 -- 1997-09-19; UA252.005.027.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - Noller, Dr. Kenneth (Medical), 1998-04 -- 1998-04; UA252.005.027.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - Noonan, Joseph (Electrical Engineering), 1994-09 -- 1994-09; UA252.005.027.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - Norman, George (Economics), 1995 -- 1998; UA252.005.027.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - Norris, Dr. Lonnie (Dental School), 1989 -- 2011; UA252.005.028.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Nutter, Deborah (Fletcher), 1995 -- 2018; UA252.005.028.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - O'Callaghar, Dr. Michael (Faculty & Staff/Vet), 1988 -- 1988; UA252.005.028.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - O'Connell, Brian (Lincoln Filene), 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.028.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - O'Donnell, Thomas F. (Medical), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.028.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - O'Leary, Father Dave (Chaplaincy), 2001-02 -- 2001-02; UA252.005.028.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - O'Leary, James P., Jr. (Asst. prof. Engineering Graphics & Design), 1964-03-30 -- 1990-05; UA252.005.028.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Oliver, Bill (Physics), 1981-09 -- 1996-10-30; UA252.005.028.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Ordovas, Dr. Jose M. (Faculty & Staff), 1986-01-16 -- 1986-08-10; UA252.005.028.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Orians, Colin M. (Biology), 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.028.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Orme-Johnson, Nanette (Biochemistry/Pharmocology), 1990-11; UA252.005.028.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - ostrander, Susan [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1980-09-04 -- 1997; UA252.005.028.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Overstrom, Eric (Faculty & Staff), 1983-10-13 -- 1999-04-28; UA252.005.028.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Pacini-Hernandez, Deborah (Anthropology), 2003 -- 2004; UA252.005.028.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Paddock, Jim (Fletcher School/Faculty and Staff), 1990 -- 1992-04-08; UA252.005.028.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Palek, Jiri M.D. (Faculty and Staff), 1987-01-30 -- 1997; UA252.005.028.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Palmer, Carole A. [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1985-05-16 -- 1999; UA252.005.028.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Palmer, Trudy (English), 1993-09 -- 1993-10; UA252.005.028.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Palubinskas, Alice [Faculty & Staff (Pres.)], 1966-02 -- 1986-03-03; UA252.005.028.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Pandlian, Natesa (Medical School), 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.028.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Panetta, Karen (Engineering), 1995-10-02 -- 2002; UA252.005.028.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Papageorge, Maria (Faculty and Staff/Dental Medicine), 1987-05 -- 1998; UA252.005.028.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Papaioannou, Virginia (Faculty and Staff), 1986 -- 1987-02-12; UA252.005.028.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Papalia, John (A & S), 1998; UA252.005.028.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Papas, Athena (Faculty & Staff), 1986-09-09 -- 2016-11-08; UA252.005.028.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Pokras, Dr. Mark (Faculty and Staff), 1986-08-26 -- 1998-03-09; UA252.005.028.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Pokras, Martha L. (faculty and Staff), 1986-01-16; UA252.005.028.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Polinna, Vincent, 1986-05 -- 1994; UA252.005.028.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Portney, Kent (Present Faculty/Staff), 1982-02-04 -- 2002; UA252.005.028.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Powell, John (Asst. Prof. Pol.Sci.), 1971-02 -- 1986-11-20; UA252.005.028.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Preis, Douglas (Faculty & Staff), 1978-10-04 -- 1986-08-27; UA252.005.028.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Puliafito, Dr. Carmen (Medical School), 1993-12-09 -- 1995-04; UA252.005.028.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Quinto, Todd (Present Faculty), 1983-12-01 -- 1992-11; UA252.005.028.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Raam, Dr. Shanthi (Faculty and Staff)], 1987-01-03 -- 1992; UA252.005.028.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Racz, Livia M. (Engineering), 1995-09-26; UA252.005.028.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Ramsey, Guthrie (Music), 1994-11-14; UA252.005.028.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Robbins, Anthony (Medical), 1999-06-22 -- 2002; UA252.005.028.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Robert, Dr. Nicholas (NEMC), 1990-05; UA252.005.028.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Roberto, John (Faculty and Staff), 1983-03-10 -- 1992-12-21; UA252.005.028.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Roberts. Susan B. (Nutrition), 1999; UA252.005.028.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Robinson, Pearl (Poly Science), 1982-12-10 -- 2005-10; UA252.005.028.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Robson, Dr. Kenneth S. (Faculty and Staff), 1966-09-11 -- 1983-03-10; UA252.005.028.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Roche, John (Fletcher), 1973-09-20 -- 1994-05-06; UA252.005.028.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Rodman, Shelley (Staff), 1996-03; UA252.005.028.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Rodriguez, Barbara (English), 1998 -- 1999-03; UA252.005.028.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Rodriguez, Walter (Engineering), 1993-09 -- 1993-10; UA252.005.028.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Rogers, Beatrice [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1983-05-31 -- 2000; UA252.005.028.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Rogers, Chris (Engineering), 1990-10 -- 1999; UA252.005.028.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Rogers, Rosemarie (Faculty & Staff), 1985-08-14 -- 1998-02-23; UA252.005.028.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Rohrer, Dr. Richard (Medical School), 1996-08-16 -- 1996-09-08; UA252.005.028.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Romain, Colleen (Medical), 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.028.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Roman, Margot [Facu;ty & Staff (Present)], 1981-01-15 -- 1983-06-06; UA252.005.028.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Romero, Christiane Z. [Faculty & Staff (Present)], 1981-03-11 -- 2001; UA252.005.028.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Romero, Michael (Biology), 1996-10-21; UA252.005.028.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Ropper, Dr. Allan, 1997-03-10; UA252.005.028.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 28, Folder 55)